quechup.com 2011-12-14

# Quechup Privacy Policy

#### Quechup Privacy Policy

This site is owned and operated by Quechup Ltd. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Quechup, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. 

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand how we gather and use of that information. 

Key points of this privacy policy: 

  * We give you choices about what personally identifiable information you share with Quechup and other Quechup members.
  * You can cancel your membership at any time.
  * We only disclose information from which you may be personally identifiable to selected third parties in accordance with this privacy policy.
  * Quechup does not send spam.
  * By using Quechup you agree to this privacy policy and our [conditions of use](http://www.quechup.com/help/terms/conditions).

####  A Special Note About Children

Children are not eligible to use our services, and we ask that minors (under the age of 16) do not submit any personal information to us.

#### Information Collection: 

Quechup gathers two types of information when you use Quechup: 

1\. Information that users provide through voluntarily registering or subscribing to our service. These are voluntary submissions requesting personal information so that we are able to provide a personalized and efficient service. 

2\. Information Quechup gathers through log files and aggregated tracking information. These files contain absolutely no personal information.

#### Information Use:

Quechup Gathers User Information In The Following Processes: 

1\. Voluntary Subscription and Use of service:   
1.1 Online Registration. Gathers e-mail, gender, date of birth, country, post code/zip code and marital status. This information is used to allow us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs and to customize our service to make your experience easier.   
1.2 Members may further optionally choose to include in their profiles a personalized description, their interests, location, employment status, photos, likes and dislikes, and other information helpful in determining like minded people and a personalized experience.   
1.3 Registered members may choose whether they wish their profile to be searchable/viewable by other registered members using the website. Your viewable profile does not include any identifying information about you, except the username you chose upon registering and your photo. 

2\. Log Files and Aggregated Tracking Information:   
2.1 Like most websites we use log files located on our servers. These include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.   
2.2 We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our website. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.   
2.3 We use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. Third party advertisers may also collect information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you, principally through the use of action beacons and/or cookies. 

#### How We Use Your Information

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the website to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. At times, we may look across multiple members to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify members multiple Member ID No. or aliases. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

You agree that in order to assist our members to meet each other we may feature members' profiles on our site and in our editorials and newsletters that we send out from time to time to our members. 

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use on the website. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. 

#### Disclosure of Information 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our website. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications always remain private. 

The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed. 

#### Financial Information. 

Under some circumstances we may require some additional information, such as, but not limited to a credit card billing address. We use this financial information, including your name, address, and other information to complete online transactions you for use of our services and to carry out anti-fraud checks and security measures for such transactions. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information on the website, you consent to our providing of your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine are necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer for their purposes. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support the transaction or activity. 

####  Advertisers. 

We use third-party advertising companies (including Google) to serve ads on our website. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Any information that these third parties collect is completely anonymous.   
Users may opt-out of the use of Google's DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

#### External Service Providers. 

There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our website. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their private policy. 

####  Other Corporate Entities. 

We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other members. Our parent and/or subsidiaries will follow privacy practices no less protective of all members than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. It is possible that Quechup and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that Quechup would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs) and we will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Legal Requests. 

Quechup cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability. 

#### Business Transitions

In the event Quechup goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

#### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) 

We may use the information collected automatically, such as your IP address, browser details, information stored via cookies, and information about how you use Quechup's Service to develop statistics and aggregate information about the number of people who visit Quechup and to customize Quechup's content, layout and features. We may share this information with third parties to help us improve the Quechup and the services we offer our users. 

#### Your Use of other Members Information 

Our services includes access to live chat (instant messaging) and member-to-member message services. As a member you have access to the Member's ID, and you might gain access to other contact information of the Member(s) through the regular use of the live chat and messaging. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree that, with respect to other Members' personally identifiable information that you obtain through live chat and messaging, Quechup hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) Quechup related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, and (b) any other purpose that such member expressly agrees to after adequate disclosure of the purpose(s). In all cases, you must give members an opportunity to remove themselves from your contacts and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this Section, can you disclose personally identifiable information about another member to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other member after adequate disclosure. Quechup and our members do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a Quechup member to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express written consent after adequate disclosure. To report spam from other Quechup members, please contact us at [spam@quechup.com](mailto:spam@quechup.com?subject=Quechup%20Spam) . 

####  Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Profile

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted during registration through the My Account Menu including: Your password and email address. You can also change your registration information such as: username, city, state, zip/post code, country, phone number, information about you, interests and what type of people you are looking to socialize with. 

Upon your written request, we will suspend your membership, contact information, and financial information from our active databases. Such information will be suspended as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our policy and applicable law. To de-activate your profile so that others cannot view it, visit the Account Summary section of My Account. 

We will retain in our files and databases information you have requested to suspend or remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. 

#### Inviting Friends and Sharing

Quechup offers services to invite friends to Quechup using terms which include, but not limited to, 'Invite Friends', 'Tell Your Friends About Quechup', 'Search Webmail Contacts' and 'Check Address Book'.  
If you choose to use these services to invite a friend to Quechup we will request and use your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a _one-time email_ inviting him or her to Quechup. The invite will contain your Quechup username as well as your real name and your email address so that your friend may easily identify who has sent the invite. Quechup stores and uses this information for the purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of referrals.

We also provide a 'share this' service, if you choose to use this we will ask for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a _one-time email_ with for the item you have shared and any additional message you included. Quechup stores and uses this information to ensure that a user can only share each item once with a particular email address, preventing the service being used to spam or harass others via Quechup. 

Your friend may [submit a request](mailto:privacy@quechup.com?subject=Invite%20Email%20Removal%20Request) that we remove this information from our database; remove requests of this nature will be completed within 30 days. 

####  Control of Your Password

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password, including fees. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your Quechup password or login information to any third parties. If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

#### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Quechup, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

#### Security

All voluntary information collected on Quechup is stored on a different, non-public access, area of our servers to the website and employs secure data networks protected by industry standard firewalls, Secure Socket Layers and password protection systems. Quechup treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Quechup by sending an e-mail to [privacy@quechup.com](mailto:privacy@quechup.com?subject=Quechup%0A%20Privacy) or to: 

Quechup Ltd, Suite 162-168 Regent St, London, W1B 5TD, United Kingdom. 

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, with notifications on members homepage and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by means of a notice on our home page or by email.  
IF ANY MODIFICATION IS UNACCEPTABLE TO YOU, YOU SHALL STOP USING QUECHUP. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF QUECHUP AND ITS SERVICE FOLLOWING OUR POSTING OF A CHANGE NOTICE OR ON OUR WEBSITE OR RECEIVING AN EMAIL NOTIFYING YOU OF A CHANGE WILL CONSTITUTE YOUR BINDING ACCEPTANCE OF THE CHANGE. 

#### Canceling membership

You have the option to cancel your membership at any time. If you are a member and no longer wish to use Quechup you can login to the site and go to My Account > Deactivate Account; then complete the simple form confirming de-activating your account. 

#### Last Revision Date

This Privacy Policy was last revised on 7 April 2009.
